Christopher Moore collection of Indian Neck Folk Festival and other recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 2: Coffeehouses and other venues
    - Gordon Bok, 2 of 2, November 22, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR086; RXK 4269; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:53:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-147.
    - Cappella Cordina, #1, possibly November 17, 1963, AFC 2016/055: SR088; RXK 4271; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:42): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Venue: Ezra Stiles College. Original ID number: S-4. Original ID number note: the reel is labeled S-74. The tape has been edited (as per the note on the box).
    - Cappella Cordina, #2, February 23, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR089; RXK 4272; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:30:20): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ezra Stiles College. Original ID number: S-5. Original ID number note: the reel is labeled S-4.
    - Cappella Cordina, #1, April 19, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR090; RXK 4273; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:21:26): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Dubbed copy. Venue: Branford College. Original ID number: S-6.
    - Cappella Cordina, #2, November 29, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR091; RXK 4274; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:33:39): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Dubbed copy. Venue: Ezra Stiles College. Original ID number: S-8.
    - Gary Davis, #1, April 17, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR094; RXK 4277; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:33:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Gary Davis, #2, April 17, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR095; RXK 4278; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:30:31): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-32.
    - Gary Davis, #3, April 17, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR096; RXK 4279; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:27:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-33.
    - Gary Davis, #4, April 17, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR097; RXK 4280; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:30:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Venue: party at Freedman's. Original ID number: S-34.
    - Gary Davis, #5, April 17, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR098; RXK 4281; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; At 00:28:00 the speed changes to 3 3/4 ips and is a recording of a phone calling an answering machine. The tape ends after this section.
      Scope and content: Venue: party at Freedman's. Original ID number: S-35.
    - Gary Davis, #1, April 16, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR092; RXK 4275; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:39:13): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-81.
    - Gary Davis, #2, April 16, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR093; RXK 4276; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:28:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-82.
    - Deep Valley Mountaineers, #2, August 26, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR099; RXK 4282; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:32:08): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The band members: Harvey Blau, Dave Howard, Dick Smith, and Lou Murray. A few seconds of yodeling can be heard near the end of the recording. Original ID number: S-74. Original ID number note: the reel is labeled S-33; the box is labeled #1.
    - Hoot at Elliot's, March 29, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR100; RXK 4283; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side A: 00:29:40, Side B: 00:32:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ramblin' Jack Elliott, Buffy Sainte-Marie. Susie Leicester, and Jon Scoville. Continued on SR101. Original ID number: S-39.
    - Hoot at Elliot's [1964-03-29]; Ralph Vaughn Williams songs [1964-03-04]; The Shags [undated], March 4, 1964, March 29, 1964, undated, AFC 2016/055: SR101; RXK 4284; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, Side A: 00:22:10, Side B: 00:29:35): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; Due to a labeling issue, the digital file designated Side A is for tape Side B, and the digital file designated Side B is for tape Side A.
      Scope and content: Side B is the continuation of the hoot from SR100. This last portion of the hoot includes a performance of "Some Stranger" by Buffy Sainte-Marie (starts about 00:06:11). She performs "Foggy Foggy Dew," starting at 00:21:55. Side A has the balance of material on the recording: the Ralph Vaughan Williams performances were sponsored by the Yale University School of Music, and the performances held at Sprague Memorial Hall. The concert ends at 00:17:21. The balance of that tape side is a recording of The Shags (not the all-female group The Shaggs, but a rock group with male voices, from the early 1960s). Original ID number: S-40.
    - Jack Elliot, #1, October 31, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR102; RXK 4285; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:36): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; The concert was held at Sprague Hall, Yale University, and sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
      Scope and content: See SR103 for part 2 of this concert, and SR104 for part 3. Original ID number: S-36.
    - Jack Elliot, #2, October 31, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR103; RXK 4286; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:37:33): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: See SR102 for part 1 of this concert (and the archivist's note), and SR104 for part 3. Original ID number: S-37.
    - Jack Elliot, #3, October 31, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR104; RXK 4287; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:19:02): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: See SR102 for part 1 of this concert (and the archivist's note), and SR103 for part 2. Original ID number: S-38.
    - Exit Coffeehouse, #1, February 26, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR105; RXK 4288; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:44:50): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; This concert was the first at The Exit's new location (1044 Chapel Street).
      Scope and content: Deep Valley Mountaineers (Dick Smith, banjo; Dave Howard, mandolin; Lou Murray, bass; Harvey Blau); Russ and Nanci Warne (announced as Mr. and Mrs. E. Russell Warne). Original ID number: S-83.
    - Exit Coffeehouse, #4, April 15, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR106; RXK 4289; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:33:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Jim McGrath; The McGowans (announced as The McGowan Brothers); The Ohio River Boys. Original ID number: S-92.
    - Marilyn Gearheart, May 8, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR107; RXK 4290; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:21:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-29.
    - Collegium Musicum, June 6, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR108; RXK 4291; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:32:20): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track; 7 in.; The first tape may not be with the collection.
      Scope and content: Karen Leicher, harpsichord; Ted Hilfiker, guitar and voice and Tim Doherty, flute; Jonathan Katz, mandolin and Karen Leicher, harpsichord; Sandra Woodard, oboe and Karen Leicher, harpsichord. Venue: Haybarn Theater, Goddard College, in Plainfield, Vermont. Written on tape box: Goddard #2. Original ID number: S-171.
    - Yale Memorial Carillon; Exit Coffeehouse, April 11, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR110; RXK 4293; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 1: 00:16:10, 2: 00:15:26, 3: 00:02:10, 4: 00:05:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; The third file is a very brief fragment of an undated 1964 Dan Ingram WABC aircheck (possibly from the week of April 7, 1964 as Dan mentions the Beatles song "Twist And Shout" is number two on the survey and the week of April 7 is the only time that song was in that position).; John David Weinland (Yale, Class of 1965) was the chairman and treasurer of the Guild of Yale University Bellringers in 1964.
      Scope and content: Side A: File 1 is a 20-minute concert by master bell ringer J. David Weinland, for the inauguration of Yale University president Kingman Brewster, Jr. File 2: folk music recorded at The Exit (coffeehouse), in April 1964: Joy Hartman [?]; Jim Else[?]. See the LC engineer's notes for information about file 3. "Yale Memorial Carillon" is the official name of the Harkness Tower Bells (as identified in the documentation). File 4: Russ Warren (also possible Warne). Probably continued from File 2. Original ID number: S-19.
    - Lou Houck, #1, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR111; RXK 4294; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; File 1: 00:48:40, File 2: 00:00:48 ): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; Track 2 is a fragment of "Wouldn't It Be Loverly" from the original Broadway cast LP of "My Fair Lady."; The initials "CM" on the related documentation may stand for Christopher Moore, but this is only conjecture. Original ID number: S-14.
    - Lou Houck, #2, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR112; RXK 4295; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:26:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips; half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-15.
    - Lou Houck, #3, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR113; RXK 4296; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; File 1: 00:10:30, File 2: 00:07:11, File 3: 00:01:53): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; There are two fragments at the end of the reel, unrelated to the main recording. The first is a very brief aircheck in half track mono format from New York City FM radio station WBFM, 101.9 FM, circa late 1963-early 1964. The brief break in the aircheck with very slow-sounding music is from what was originally recorded on the tape in full track format and is part of fragment two, and can be heard in full and at correct speed there.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-16.
    - Susie Leicester, January 29, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR116; RXK 4299; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:47:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-65.
    - Med School Horror Show, #1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR119; RXK 4302; 1 sound tape reel (acetate and polyester, 00:46:02): analog, 7 1/2 ips; half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Senior show. Original ID number: S-75.
    - The New Strangers, #1, March 14, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR120; RXK 4303; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:38:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The New Strangers (Danny Kalb, Sam Charters); Venue: Yale Law School. Original ID number: S-21.
    - The New Strangers, #2, March 14, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR121; RXK 4304; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:26:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The New Strangers (Danny Kalb, Sam Charters); Venue: Yale Law School. Original ID number: S-22.
    - The New Strangers, #3, March 14, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR122; RXK 4305; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:26:16): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The New Strangers (Danny Kalb, Sam Charters); Venue: Yale Law School. Original ID number: S-23.
    - Old Time Fiddlers contest, #1, June 1968, July 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR123; RXK 4306; 1 sound tape reel (acetate and polyester, 00:44:50): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo and mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Kevin Sicard sings and plays guitar (from near the start until about 00:07:33); recorded in June 1968. The fiddle contest begins about 00:07:49. The performers for that section of the recording include Harry Stark with Bob Manning, Bill Royer, and Merle Dubry. Venue for the contest: Craftsbury Common, Vermont. The tape box has the date as July 27; an accompanying slip of paper has July 28. Continued on SR124. Original ID number: S-128.
    - Old Time Fiddlers contest, #2, July 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR124; RXK 4307; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:50:36): analog, 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo and mono; 7 in.; There are two speed changes on this tape: one from 7 1/2 ips to 3 3/4 ips at 00:21:10 and from 3 3/4 ips back to 7 1/2 ips at 00:26:12. There are also incidents of audio from the original contents of the tape at 00:25:15 to 00:22:25; and at the end of the tape from 00:48:16 to 00:50:36. The unintended audio is presented "as is" because both instances are brief and because they are not part of the intended program.
      Scope and content: Wayne Young, Tony Washburn, Florence Mercier (Raymond Mercier's sister, who plays piano to Washburn's fiddle on "Canadian Jig"), Wildred Guillette, unidentified bagpiper, Wayne Perry, Dick Blaustein (announced as Richard Blaustein), Patrick Bowden, Donald Sandville, John Burke, Tim Woodbridge, and Allan Block. Venue: Craftsbury Common, Vermont. Continued from SR123; continued on SR125. Original ID number: S-129.
    - Old Time Fiddlers contest, #3, July 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR125; RXK 4308; 1 sound tape reel (acetate and polyester, 00:48:02): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo and mono; 7 in.; From 00:35:40 to the end of the file/tape, the audio is the original content of the tape before being used to record the live performances of the Old Time Fiddlers Contest (unidentified classical music recorded from unknown sources).
      Scope and content: Joe Gagne, Lou Anne Grow and Rod Fuller (Fuller plays bones), Bunny Kop [?] and Vera Vandon [?], Clint Myhill, Caden Tibbets and Wayne Perry, Harold Luce and Donna Weston (piano), Elwin Corey, Ozzie Ploof, and Henry LaRocque. Venue: Craftsbury Common, Vermont. Continued from SR124. Original ID number: S-130.
    - Old Timey Concert, #1, circa 1967-1968, AFC 2016/055: SR126; RXK 4309; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side A: 00:28:15, Side B: 00:25:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Bill Hamilton and the Ohio River Boys (Harvey Blau, Mark Leshter, and Tom Rosson); The Vermont Country Fiddlers Band. Venue: Yale University. Continued on SR127. Original ID number: S-113.
    - Old Timey Concert, #2, circa 1967-1968, AFC 2016/055: SR127; RXK 4310; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side A: 00:27:07, Side B: 00:23:08): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The Vermont Country Fiddlers Band, the Grandfather Brothers (Lou Sellinger and Richard Blaustein), Bill Hamilton and the Ohio River Boys, and Bill Clark. Continued from SR126; continued on SR128. Original ID number: S-114.
    - Old Timey Concert, #3, circa 1967-1968, AFC 2016/055: SR128; RXK 4311; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side A: 00:17:00, Side B: 00:03:04): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; The audio on Side B is unrelated to the collection, and appears to be the original contents of the tape before being used again.
      Scope and content: Bill Clark; Wayne Young, Charlie Leiden, and Bob Black [?]; The Grandfather Brothers. Continued from SR127. Original ID number: S-115.
    - Ed O'Reilly, June 1969, August 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR129; RXK 4312; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side A: 00:46:00, Side B: 00:33:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter-track, stereo; 7 in.; Occasional speed issues (from the source tape).
      Scope and content: Ed O'Reilly and friend (vocals). Songs include works sung a cappella and others accompanied by guitar. Recordist is "Harry." Original ID number: S-172.
    - Ed O'Reilly, March 23, 1975, AFC 2016/055: SR132; RXK 4315; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:43:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo and mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Venue: Stone Soup Coffeehouse, Pawtucket, Rhode Island. Original ID number: S-188.
    - Ed O'Reilly, March 23, 1975, AFC 2016/055: SR133; RXK 4316; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:40:55): analog, 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Venue: Stone Soup Coffeehouse, Pawtucket, Rhode Island. Original ID number: S-189.
    - Ed O'Reilly, March 25, 1975, AFC 2016/055: SR134; RXK 4317; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:29:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-186.
    - Ed O'Reilly, March 25, 1975, AFC 2016/055: SR135; RXK 4318; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:30:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-187.
    - Ed O'Reilly and Andy Woolf (1 of 2), Winter 1973, AFC 2016/055: SR130; RXK 4313; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo and mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ed O'Reilly and Andy Woolf. Venue: Cambridge. Original ID number: S-183.
    - Ed O'Reilly and Andy Woolf (2 of 2), Winter 1973, AFC 2016/055: SR131; RXK 4314; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:09:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo and mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ed O'Reilly and Andy Woolf. Venue: Cambridge. Original ID number: S-182.
    - Original Student Compositions (concert), April 25, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR136; RXK 4319; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:43:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Part of the Yale Arts Festival (Yale University). The concert was held in the Silliman Common Room, Silliman College. Includes both vocal and instrumental works. Original ID number: S-111.
    - Carol Sudhalter (flute) and Ray Loring (piano) (1 of 2), March 26, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR137; RXK 4320; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:10:32): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Presented by Lowell House. Original ID number: S-176.
    - Carol Sudhalter (flute) and Ray Loring (piano) (2 of 2), March 26, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR138; RXK 4321; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:43:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Presented by Lowell House. Original ID number: S-177.
    - Rick and Lorraine Lee, #1, November 6, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR139; RXK 4322; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:43:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track; 7 in.
      Scope and content: "Tom" is also credited on this reel. "Cabin Fever" (as documented on the tape boxes for SR139, SR140, and SR141) is the name for the musical group. See notes for AFC 2016/002: SR191. Multiple takes of songs as well as false starts are included. Continued on SR140. Original ID number: S-167.
    - Rick and Lorraine Lee, #2, November 6, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR140; RXK 4323; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:43:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Multiple takes of songs as well as false starts are included. See the note for SR139. Continued from SR139; continued on SR141. Original ID number: S-168.
    - Rick and Lorraine Lee, #3, November 6, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR141; RXK 4324; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:15:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Multiple takes of songs as well as false starts are included. See the note for SR139. Continued from SR140. Original ID number: S-169.
    - Rick and Lorraine Lee (1 of 2), January 6, 1974, AFC 2016/055: SR142; RXK 4325; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:45:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Multiple takes of songs as well as false starts are included. Continued from SR143. Original ID number: S-184.
    - Rick and Lorraine Lee (2 of 2), January 6, 1974, AFC 2016/055: SR143; RXK 4326; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:11:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Multiple takes of songs as well as false starts are included. Continued from SR142. Original ID number: S-185. Original ID number note: the reel is labeled S-32.
    - Rick and Lorraine Lee, January 23, 1978, AFC 2016/055: SR144; RXK 4327; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:45:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Other musicians on this recording include Connie Hume (whistle), Winnie Winston (steel guitar), George Wilson (bass), Frank Hume (Fender), and Bill Spence (hammered dulcimer).
    - Yizhak Schotten, #1, November 21, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR145; RXK 4328; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:28:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Schotten performs classical works on the viola, accompanied by two or three other musicians. Recorded in the Junior Common Room, Adams House, Harvard University. Original ID number: S-173.
    - Ed Schwartz, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR146; RXK 4329; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:27:20): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; The tape was not erased before being used. As a result, aside from the intended content for this tape (Ed Schwartz), there is other material on the tape. The first is "Events for Tape Recorder" by Mel Powell, then various sine wave tones, a recording of WNYC-FM radio dial surfing that doesn't linger on any one station for too long, and remnants of two telephone calls at the very end of the tape that were recorded at 1 7/8 ips.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-30.
    - Jon Scoville, #1, March 22 and March 24, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR147; RXK 4330; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:30:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: All songs are guitar instrumentals. Original ID number: S-66.
    - Jon Scoville, #2, March 24, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR148; RXK 4331; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:32:35): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: All songs are guitar instrumentals. Original ID number: S-67.
    - Jon Scoville and Pat Pierce, #3, July 28, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR149; RXK 4332; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:14:26): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Instruments include guitar and harmonica; some vocals. Original ID number: S-70. Original ID number note: the reel is labeled S-36.
    - Jon Scoville and Pat Pierce, #4, August 7, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR150; RXK 4333; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:30:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Instruments include guitar and harmonica; some vocals. Original ID number: S-71.
    - Jon Scoville and Pat Pierce, #5; plus Soul Toads Garbage, August 7, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR151; RXK 4334; 1 sound tape reel (acetate, 00:31:18): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Performance by Scoville and Pierce ends about 00:04:14, following immediately by what is assumed to be Soul Toads Garbage, a rock band recorded during a live performance in an unidentified venue in 1965. Original ID number: S-72. Original ID number note: the reel is labeled S-70.
    - Solomon's Seal, reel #1, November 20, 1982, AFC 2016/055: SR152; RXK 4335; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:44:20): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Solomon's Seal is a quartet comprised of Rick and Lorraine Lee, Jane Orzechowski (fiddle), and Sarah F. Bauhan [Sarah Bauhan] (whistle). Continued on SR153.
    - Solomon's Seal, reel #2, November 20, 1982, AFC 2016/055: SR153; RXK 4336; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:42:37): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Continued from SR152; continued on SR154. See the note for SR152.
    - Solomon's Seal, reel #3, November 20, 1982, AFC 2016/055: SR154; RXK 4337; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:46:52): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; About 00:07:49, Christopher Moore (as Chris Moore) is acknowledged as the person doing the sound for the performance, from the company Ursa Major.; The audio after 00:19:20 is the original content of the tape before being used to record the concert. It was backwards on the reel but reversed for the digital file. The audio is inconsequential in terms of content, and included for the sake of completeness.